Alvieto Haykal

Surabaya, Indonesia | haykalcs@gmail.com | (62) 822-3489-7335 linkedin.com/in/alvietomhf | alvietomhf.qithub.io

Fullstack Developer

A skilled, competent, and diligent individual, specializing in the fullstack web development (Laravel/CI - Go/Fiber - NodeJS/Express/Nest - ReactJS/Next). For the last 3 years, I have been developing applications using PHP, Go, JavaScript & TypeScript programming languages. I love coding and am interested in solving problems while coding. I've hands on in all stages of the programming cycle, from planning to development and deployment. No two days are the same for me; my tasks may involve analyzing algorithms, altering code, fixing bugs, brainstorming ideas for integrating new systems.

Experience

Fullstack Developer, PT Bimasakti Multi Sinergi (Sept 2022 – present)

- Maintain and develop features SpeedCash:
 - API for inquiry, payment and reporting
 - o Poin and multipayment feature
 - SpedCash web version and landing page
 - UBP (utility bill payment)
 - KYC verification
 - Bulk transfer internal/disbursement
 - Firebase notification sender
- Maintain and develop features TiketKAI:
 - Update payment method using payment gateway
 - o Integration with biller for booking and payment
 - Back-office application
- Maintain and develop features Micrommerce:
 - o Authentication with OTP
 - Chat service using XMPP instant messaging
 - o Product management
 - Order management
 - Cashout management
 - o Integration with RajaOngkir and linked account SpeedCash

Backend Developer, Runshop (Aug 2021 - Jan 2022)

- Integration with H2H provider
- Integration with payment gateway
- Bank mutation checker
- Scrapper payment with third party
- Telegram notification sender

Backend Developer, PT Kipa Teknologi Indonesia (Jan 2021 – Feb 2021) Internship

Developed a project called Sadean:

- Authentication module using JWT
- Customer management
- Product management
- Email and Firebase notification sender

Skills

- Laravel, CI
- Go, Fiber
- NodeJS, Express, Nest
- ReactJS, Next
- Redis, Memcached
- RabbitMQ, Kafka

- PHP
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- HTML, CSS
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Docker, Kubernetes
- GitHub, Gitlab CICD

Certifications

- Pelaksana Sistem Pembayaran dan Pengelolaan Uang Rupiah Subbidang Pengelolaan Transfer Dana Lembaga Selain Bank (APPUI WIDYANTARA INDONESIA, 2024) Backend Developer Expert (Dicoding Indonesia, 2021)

Education

Universitas Negeri Surabaya, Teknik Informatika (2018 - 2022)

Languages

- English
- Bahasa Indonesia